<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HIM Type Definition Rule Set on Hierarchical Information Model</title>
    <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/type_definition_rule_set/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HIM Type Definition Rule Set on Hierarchical Information Model</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:37:03 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/type_definition_rule_set/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Type Definition Model</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/type_definition_rule_set/basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/type_definition_rule_set/basics/</guid>
      <description>A type_definition tree contains data type definitions that are not part of the primitive datatypes defined by HIM.
The currently supported node types are suited for definition of structs.
Node Types The node types for representing type definitions are:
Branch Struct Property Please see more information about these node types here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Property node</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/type_definition_rule_set/property/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:37:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/type_definition_rule_set/property/</guid>
      <description>Data represented by the node type property have a relationship to any other data having the same struct parent in that they are all sampled in an &amp;ldquo;atomic&amp;rdquo; operation, i.e. the set of data points have the same timestamp representing the sample time.
Nodes of the type property must have the following mandatory metadata:
Name Type Datatype Description For more information, see the Common Rule Set: Mandatory Metadata.
Besides the mandatory metadata mentioned above, the following optional metadata may be used</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Struct node</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/type_definition_rule_set/struct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:37:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/type_definition_rule_set/struct/</guid>
      <description>A struct node type may be used to represent multiple data points that have the relationship that they are always sampled in an &amp;ldquo;atomic&amp;rdquo; operation, i. e. the set of samples have the same timestamp. An example of such a set of data points are the GPS dta points latitude, longitude, height.
This node type is only allowed in trees of the information types typedefinition or service. For more information, please see respective parts of this document.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
