<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Common Node types on Hierarchical Information Model</title>
    <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/common_rule_set/node_types/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Common Node types on Hierarchical Information Model</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:37:03 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/common_rule_set/node_types/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Branch node</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/common_rule_set/node_types/branch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:37:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/common_rule_set/node_types/branch/</guid>
      <description>The interior of a HIM tree is built up of nodes that have the node type branch.
Nodes of the type branch must have the following mandatory metadata:
Name Type Description For more information, see the Common Rule Set: Mandatory Metadata.
Besides the mandatory metadata mentioned above, the following optional metadata may be used
Comment Instances Aggregate For more information, please see the Common Rule Set: Optional Metadata.
The root node of a HIM tre must be of the node type branch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Property node</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/common_rule_set/node_types/property/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:37:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/common_rule_set/node_types/property/</guid>
      <description>Sensors are signals to read values of properties in a vehicle. Values of sensors typically change over time. Reading a sensor shall return the current actual value of the related property, e.g. the current speed or the current position of the seat.
Nodes of the type property must have the following mandatory metadata:
Name Type Datatype Description For more information, see the Common Rule Set: Mandatory Metadata.
Besides the mandatory metadata mentioned above, the following optional metadata may be used</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Struct node</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/common_rule_set/node_types/struct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:37:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/common_rule_set/node_types/struct/</guid>
      <description>The node type struct is only allowed in trees of the information types typedefinition or service. For more information, please see respective parts of this document.
Nodes of the type struct must have the following mandatory metadata:
Name Type Description For more information, see the Common Rule Set: Mandatory Metadata.
Besides the mandatory metadata mentioned above, the following optional metadata may be used
Comment For more information, please see the Common Rule Set: Optional Metadata.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
