<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HIM Resource Data Rule Set on Hierarchical Information Model</title>
    <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/resource_data_rule_set/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HIM Resource Data Rule Set on Hierarchical Information Model</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 13:05:11 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/resource_data_rule_set/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/resource_data_rule_set/basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 13:05:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/resource_data_rule_set/basics/</guid>
      <description>It is the leaf nodes of a tree that represents and defines the actual data. The definition is expressed by metadata describing the data associated to the node.
Node Types The node types for representing data entries are:
Sensor Actuator Attribute Please see the respective chapters for more information about these node types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actuator node</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/resource_data_rule_set/actuator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:37:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/resource_data_rule_set/actuator/</guid>
      <description>Actuators are used to control the desired value of a property. Some properties in a vehicle cannot change instantly. A typical example is position of a seat or a window. Reading a value of an actuator shall return the current actual value, e.g. the current position of the seat, rather than the wanted/desired position. A typical example could be if someone wants to change the position of a seat from 0 to 100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sensor node</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/resource_data_rule_set/sensor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:37:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/resource_data_rule_set/sensor/</guid>
      <description>Sensors are signals to read values of properties in a vehicle. Values of sensors typically change over time. Reading a sensor shall return the current actual value of the related property, e.g. the current speed or the current position of the seat.
Nodes of the type sensor must have the following mandatory metadata:
Name Type Datatype Description For more information, see the Common Rule Set: Mandatory Metadata.
Besides the mandatory metadata mentioned above, the following optional metadata may be used</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attribute node</title>
      <link>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/resource_data_rule_set/attribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 12:37:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://covesa.github.io/hierarchical_information_model/resource_data_rule_set/attribute/</guid>
      <description>Nodes of the types attribute must have the following mandatory metadata:
Name Type Datatype Default Description For more information, see the Common Rule Set: Mandatory Metadata.
Besides the mandatory metadata mentioned above, the following optional metadata may be used
Unit Comment For more information, please see the Common Rule Set: Optional Metadata.
This node type must have a node of type branch as parent, and must not have any children.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
